tellapal.com 2015-06-08

# privacy policy | Extole

Effective on June 5, 2015

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, [www.extole.com](http://www.extole.com/), www.tellapal.com and our service platform and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Extole Inc.

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Extole participates in the U.S.–E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce. As part of our [participation](http://export.gov/safeharbor/) in the safe harbor, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Framework. If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor you should first contact us (as provided above). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by [Internet here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request), fax to 415-520-3420, or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., [click for mailing address](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us). If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, click [here](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/dispute-resolution-services/) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.

This privacy policy describes how Extole, Inc. (“Extole”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web sites: [www.extole.com](http://www.extole.com/) and [www.tellapal.com](http://www.tellapal.com/), as well as the data collected at the Extole applications and wherever this privacy policy is posted. Please note that for data collected through Extole applications, Extole is acting as a data processor and service provider and collecting the data on behalf of our business clients (“Clients”). Extole collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. Extole works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected.

Extole complies with the U.S.–E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.–Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Extole has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Extole’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

## Website Visitors

Except as described below, Extole does not collect or require users of its service, http://www.extole.com/, http://www.tellapal.com, to furnish personal information. Like most websites, Extole collects non-personal information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring/exit pages, and the date and time of each visitor request, browser type, and operating system. Extole’s purpose in collecting non-personal information is to better understand how Extole’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Extole may release non-personal information in the aggregate, for example, by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its service.

Extole also collects potentially personal information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Extole does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personal information, as described below.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you when you visit our website:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, phone number
  * Information about your business such as company name

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to

  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Enable you to post your resume, search job postings, and contact or be contacted by prospective employers

In addition Extole provides the technology to promote referral-marketing campaigns for our clients. Extole enables certain users to participate in or promote referral-marketing campaigns for advertisers on the Extole network. Those users who would like to participate in an Extole campaign require Extole to know a little bit more about them, i.e., personal information. To participate in an Extole campaign, users must provide certain personal information, such as their name and email address. Extole does not disclose personal information other than as described below. And users can always refuse to supply personal information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities (i.e. participating in an Extole campaign). 

Extole also has functionality where we may collect some of your personal information through the Facebook Connect and the Graph API. Your data will be shared with us from Facebook. We use Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider to authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form and to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

For our Facebook applications we also use Facebook Permissions in order to give you the option to share personal information like your activities and interests as well as the authorization to post information about your activity to your profile page. All personal information that may be collected is done so via an iframe or through a Facebook application on behalf of our client. Please refer to the privacy policy on the site/iframe where this data is collected.

Extole will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed provide services to our Client. Extole will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities: 

  * hosting company
  * CRM

These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us. We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal or bankruptcy process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Extole is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Extole, Inc. may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. 

## Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Extole, Inc. and our partners [specify type e.g. marketing partners], affiliates, or analytics or service providers [specify type e.g. online customer support provider, etc]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for [our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication]. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LS such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LS.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our sites, you can contact us as described below.

## Links to Other Sites

Our site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas might be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us as described below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site and everywhere else it is posted.

## Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@extole.com.

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Import Contacts

You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our website. We collect the username and password for the email account from which you wish to import your contacts, and will only use your personal information for that purpose.

## Communications from Us

If you register for any of the Extole programs and applications, you may receive promotional communications on behalf of our client. You can opt out of these by unsubscribing through the unsubscribe link in the email.

## Updating of Personal information, and Opt-Out

Extole permits its visitors to freely update, correct or delete any personal information maintained by Extole. To do so, visitors need only look for the links and other tools available on Extole’s website or contact Extole by email. Visitors who no longer wish to receive materials distributed pursuant to an Extole mailing list should notify Extole by the same means.

Extole has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, who seeks to correct, amend, delete inaccurate data or withdraw consent to further contact should direct his/her query to the Extole’s Client (the data controller). We will respond to requests for access within 30 days.

## Behavioral Advertising

We may partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here <http://preferences.truste.com/truste/> (or if located in the European Union [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us as described below. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. If you would like the information we hold about you deleted, please contact us as described below. We will respond to your request within 30 business days, and delete your data within 60 business days.

## Membership Eligibility

Extole’s services are available only to, and may only be used by individuals who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. Without limiting the foregoing, Extole’s services are not available to children (persons under the age of 18) or to temporarily or indefinitely suspended Extole members. If you do not qualify, please do not use Extole service. Further, your Extole account (including feedback) and User ID may not be transferred or sold to another third party.

## Fraud

Without limiting any other remedies, Extole may suspend or terminate your account if it suspects that you (by conviction, settlement, insurance or escrow investigation, or otherwise) have engaged in fraudulent activity in connection with the Extole service.

## Restricted Activities

Your use of the Extole service to participate in certain Extole campaigns shall not: (a) be false, inaccurate or misleading; (b) be fraudulent or involve the sale of illegal services or items; (c) infringe any third party’s copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy; (d) violate any applicable law, statute, professional code of conduct, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to restrictions on sharing of fees, restrictions on giving referral fees, consumer protection, unfair competition, anti-discrimination or false advertising); (e) be defamatory, trade libelous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing; (f) be obscene or contain child pornography; (g) contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, easter eggs or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information; (h) create liability for us or cause us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISPs or other suppliers; and (i) link directly or indirectly to or include descriptions of goods or services that are prohibited under this Agreement or ones that you do not have a right to link to or include.

## License

Solely to enable Extole to use the information you supply us with, so that we are not violating any rights you might have in that information, you agree to grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sub-licensable (through multiple tiers) right to exercise the copyright, publicity, and database rights (but no other rights) you have in your information, in any media now known or not currently known, with respect to your information. Extole will only use your information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

## Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Information

You can contact us by writing at the address below:  
225 Bush Street, 16th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
or email us at [support@extole.com](mailto:support@extole.com)
